Muhammed **Asaad** Nadeem

REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER



Address

Guiranwala, Pakistan

Email Address asaadxheikh_1@yahoo.com

Date Of Birth

24 December 1997

Linkedin

Asaad Sheikh

Github asaadxheikh

Stackoverflow

Asaad Sheikh

SKILLS

✔ React native. React

Advanced ••••

Express, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, **Firebase** Advanced ••••

✓ Node.js,

✔ Google Maps, Mapbox

Advanced ...

✓ JavaScript (ES5/ES6/ES7+, Babel) Advanced ••••

✓ Webpack,

✔ Redux, Thunk, Hooks, Web API, **REST APIs**

Adnavced ••••

Gulp, Babel, npm, yarn, etc... Basic ●●

HOBBIES

Cricket

Running

Chess

OBJECTIVE

I'm a full-stack developer who's working with the latest and most effective technologies. The main stack of technologies I specialize in is JavaScript plus frameworks/libraries for three years. I love bringing design to live and creating beautiful, usable experience for all users. Good interpersonal skills to build good working relationship. Excellent team player with global mindset.

WORK EXPERIENCE

My.Organics

Full stack react native developer

(November 2020 - June 2021)

Worked as a full stack react native developer with My.oragins venice Italy to develop their Ecommerce mobile app with complex operation between dealers, shop owner and end users.

UpWork as a freelauncer

(July 2021 - February 2022)

React native developer

Worked as a react native freelauncer during this pandemic.

EDUCATION

University of Central Punjab

(September 2016 - September 2020)

3.93

PROJECTS

Comma Barber Booking app

https://apps.apple.com/tt/app/comma-barbers-bookingapp/id1601934663

Bachelor Degree Bachelor of computer science

(February 2021 - December

2021)

Comma barbers booking app is a mobile platform for barbers and customers to manage bookings online. It also connects barbershops and independent barbers to work together.

Comma barbers booking app is a mobile platform for barbers and clients to enhance barbershop experience.

An all-in-one platform to power your barbershop operations.

Comma Find Barbers

https://apps.apple.com/tt/app/comma-findbarbers/id1601995010

(February 2021 - December

2021)

Comma Find barbers is a mobile platform for customers to find the barbershops and independent barbers near you and manage bookings online.

Comma Find Barbers booking app is a mobile platform for barbers and clients to enhance Customer experience.

Explore and book best barbers near you.

MY.ORGANICS

https://apps.apple.com/be/app/my-organics/id1552454809

(November 2020 - February 2021)

On the MY.ORGANICS App you will find the exclusive range of products for scalp, hair, and skincare, created with balanced formulas based on the best plant extracts. MY.ORGANICS create exclusive products for hair care, formulated from certifie

and grown with organic and biodynamic farming techniques. Each MY.ORGANICS product that you will find on the APP contains high concentrations of

pure essential oils, extracted from plants and flowers with traditional and secular harvesting techniques to obtain products composed of 100% natural ingredients.

LANGUAGES

English

Urdu Native

Fluent Arabic

Understandabe